allears.net 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy - AllEars.Net

AllEarsNet LLC, (AllEarsNet) owns and operates **AllEars.net®** , which comprises **the Unofficial Walt Disney World Information Guide** , the **ALL EARS®** weekly newsletter and its companion promotional newsletter **Ears the Deal™**.

AllEarsNet has created this **privacy statement** in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the users' privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for **AllEars.net** **®.**

**AllEars.net® is committed to your privacy, and does not sell, exchange, or release any of your individual personal information to a third party.**

### SCOPE OF POLICY

This Privacy Policy applies only to **AllEars.net** **®**. This privacy policy does not apply to other companies' or organizations' websites that you may link to. You should carefully review the Privacy Policy of other websites to determine how they treat personal information. 

### INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED AND STORED

When you browse through any web site, certain personal information about you can be collected. Like most standard web site servers we use log files. We automatically collect and temporarily store information about your visit. We use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. The data collected may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, domain name, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This data is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Your IP number is visible to most of the websites that you visit. **AllEars.net** **®** may use IP numbers to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Web site. 

**AllEars.net®** utilizes **a number of outside vendors to operate portions of the website and/or newsletter. For instance,[campaigner.com](http://campaigner.com/)**, drip.com and InfusionSoft are used for newsletter ( **ALL EARS®** and **Ears the Deal** ™) distribution, and **[adspeed.com](http://adspeed.com/)** for banner ad programs. Please see those sites for their privacy information.

### PERSONALLY PROVIDED INFORMATION

The only personally identifiable information about you that is collected is that which you provide on a voluntary basis. We make every effort to ensure that whatever information you provide is maintained in a secure environment. 

AllEarsNet will not knowingly or intentionally disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our visitors, unless required for law enforcement or statute. 

If you choose to subscribe to our weekly newsletter, **ALL EARS®** , you will have to provide an e-mail address. **ALL EARS®** is only delivered electronically.

AllEarsNet utilizes **[adspeed.com](http://adspeed.com/)** for banner rotation and statistics. **[adspeed.com](http://adspeed.com/)** maintains information on each visitor and all associated data for the last 30 days. Other information is kept in compact forms. **[adspeed.com](http://adspeed.com/)** also tracks how many people are currently active on the site, where they are and came from, which ads were viewed at what time. AllEarsNet® webmasters have access to this information. 

### INFORMATION USE

We reserve the right to perform statistical analysis of user behavior and characteristics while visiting this site. We do this in order to measure interest in and use of the site. We may share this information in the aggregate with advertisers or potential advertisers. We will use information to let advertisers know how many visitors have seen their banners and how many have clicked on them. We provide only aggregate data from these analyses to third parties. Advertisers will not be able to identify any individual from the data provided.

### COOKIES

A cookie is a mechanism that allows a website to record your comings and goings, usually without your knowledge or consent. **ALL EARS® does not require cookies of its visitors.** However, our banner rotation program is administered by a third party and may contain cookies. We do not have access to this cookie information. We use Google Analytics to track website usage, visitors, what pages are viewed, and obtain aggregate demographics. We can not see your personal information. 

If you do not want to accept cookies from **AllEars.net** **®** or other sites, you must set your browser software to not accept cookies. Look in the Preferences (Netscape) or Internet Options (Microsoft Internet Explorer) feature to disable cookies. 

If you disable cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the **AllEars.net®** websites. Also, the disabling of cookies may prohibit your participation in contests and drawings.

### REGISTRATION FORMS 

The only registration form is for subscription to **ALL EARS®** , the weekly newsletter sent to subscribers' e-mail addresses. 

The **ALL EARS®** registration form **requires** users to provide an e-mail address and **requests** demographic information (like zip code and country). Contact information from the registration forms is used to send out the newsletter and to gather aggregate demographic data. The demographic information is shared with advertisers and partners on an aggregate basis only.

**ALL EARS®** subscribers have the option to sign up for **Ears the Deal™** mailing, which is special offers and announcements pertaining to Disney World and Central Florida. By opting in to this mailing you agree to have your email address added to an **AllEarsNet®** special mailing list.

**Individual information is never shared with any third party. AllEars.net® does NOT sell your email address or distribute it to any other entity.**

**ALL EARS® is ONLY delivered via e-mail.** If the user does not provide an email address, **ALL EARS®** can not be delivered. An archive of the featured articles of previous issues is available at the **ALL EARS website**.

### SURVEYS AND CONTESTS

Occasionally our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). **Depending on the estimated retail value of the prize, you may be required to submit your Social Security Number for issuance of a US Tax Form 1099. Contact information will be used and shared with the contest sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes.**

**Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Your personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties.** We provide only aggregate data to third parties. Advertisers will not be able to identify any individual from the data provided.

### LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES

This site contains hyperlinks to web sites operated by parties other than AllEarsNet. Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only. AllEarsNet does not control such web sites, has not reviewed such websites and is not responsible for their contents. The inclusion of hyperlinks to such web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such web sites or any association with their operators. Linking to any off-site pages is at your own risk.

AllEarsNet is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. **This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.**

### SECURITY

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We are aware of your privacy concerns and strive to collect only as much data as is required to make your use of this site as efficient and satisfying as possible.

### SPECIAL NOTICE TO PARENTS AND GUARDIANS

**ALL EARS NET®** does not intentionally seek personal information about minors who visit this web site or subscribe to the **ALL EARS®** newsletter. **AllEarsNet®** encourages you to ask your children to seek your permission before providing information about themselves or their family over the Internet.

### SPECIAL NOTICE TO CHILDREN

**IF YOU ARE UNDER 18 YEARS OLD, PLEASE HAVE YOUR PARENT/GUARDIAN READ THIS POLICY COMPLETELY. PLEASE ASK YOUR PARENT/GUARDIAN TO EXPLAIN IT TO YOU IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS. Ask your parent or guardian for permission before you send any personal information over the Internet.**

Our policy, with respect to the collection by other organizations of personal information from children at our site is: AllEarsNet does not have any agreements with outside organizations to collect personal information at our site.

### DISCLOSURE EXCEPTIONS

Notwithstanding the above policies, AllEarsNet reserves the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if required to do so by law or if AllEarsNet believes that such action is necessary:

* To comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order;

* To protect the Company's rights and property;

* To investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening or abusive messages;

* To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the AllEarsNet websites; or

* During emergencies, such as when AllEarsNet reasonably believes someone's physical safety is at risk. 

### DATA ACCESS 

At any time, you can change choices you have previously made as to the use of your personal information. Every ALL EARS® subscriber mailing will clearly contain an opt-out and/or unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email, allowing you to withdraw your permission for future mailings. Alternatively, you can send a blank email to: admin@allears.net and type "REMOVE" in the subject field. Permission changes will be honored as soon as possible after receipt. Please allow seven days for processing.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, contact:

This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 12, 2018.
